<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Container version="2">
  <Name>ghostboard-server</Name>
  <Repository>thehelpfulidiot/ghostboard-server</Repository>
  <Registry>https://hub.docker.com/r/thehelpfulidiot/ghostboard-server</Registry>
  <Network>bridge</Network>
  <MyIP/>
  <Shell>sh</Shell>
  <Privileged>false</Privileged>
  <Support>https://forums.unraid.net/topic/122788-support-jpdvm2014-templates/</Support>
  <Project>https://github.com/jon6fingrs/ghostboard</Project>
  <Overview>Ghostboard is a lightweight, self-hosted solution for real-time synchronized text sharing. This repository includes a WebSocket server for syncing text across multiple clients and a command-line client for retrieving or updating the shared text.&#xD;
&#xD;
This project is aimed at self-hosters who want to quickly and easily share text between devices. There is no encryption or security&#x2014;it is not suitable for deployment on the internet or other untrusted networks. Ghostboard creates a simple webpage that accepts text, which is mirrored across all connected instances. A command-line client is also provided for interacting with the text without requiring a graphical interface.&#xD;
Features&#xD;
&#xD;
    Server:&#xD;
        Serves a webpage with a real-time synchronized text field.&#xD;
        Clients see live updates as text is typed.&#xD;
        Text remains synchronized across all connected clients.&#xD;
        New Feature: Dynamically create multiple boards based on the URL path. Each unique subdirectory (e.g., /test or /example) hosts an independent board with its own synchronized text field.&#xD;
&#xD;
</Overview>
  <Category>Productivity: Tools:</Category>
  <WebUI>http://[IP]:[PORT:8080]/</WebUI>
  <TemplateURL/>
  <Icon>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/jon6fingrs/ghostboard/main/icon.png</Icon>
  <ExtraParams/>
  <PostArgs/>
  <CPUset/>
  <DateInstalled>1738028432</DateInstalled>
  <DonateText>If you find this template useful, I’d love a coffee!</DonateText>
  <DonateLink>https://bmc.link/JPDVM2014</DonateLink>
  <Requires/>
  <Config Name="WebUI" Target="80" Default="8080" Mode="tcp" Description="" Type="Port" Display="always" Required="true" Mask="false">8080</Config>
</Container>
